Inauguration 2009 Sermons and Orations Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Submissions, 2008-2009
  - Refuge and Strength Full Gospel Assembly (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Sermon, 2009-02-01, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0305_sr01 (Box 18)
First Baptist Church (Franklin, Ind.) afc2009001_0071
First Baptist Church in Needham (Needham, Mass.) afc2009001_0272
First Christian Church (Mount Vernon, Wash.) afc2009001_0157
First Christian Church of Turlock (Turlock, Calif.) afc2009001_0012
First Parish Church, Unitarian Universalist (Fitchburg, Mass.) afc2009001_0028
First Church of Christ, Scientist (Springfield, Ill.) afc2009001_0238
First Church Unitarian (Littleton, Mass.) afc2009001_0153
First Congregational United Church of Christ (Vancouver, Wash.) afc2009001_0288
First Parish Church (Ashby, Mass.) afc2009001_0021
First Presbyterian Church (Ann Arbor, Mich.) afc2009001_0235
First Presbyterian Church (Hamilton Square, N.J.) afc2009001_0218
First Presbyterian Church (Holland, Mich.) afc2009001_0231
First Unitarian Church of Oklahoma City afc2009001_0096
First Unitarian Church of Salt Lake City afc2009001_0294
First Unitarian Society (Madison, Wis.) afc2009001_0226
First Unitarian Society (Minneapolis, Minn.) afc2009001_0222
First United Methodist Church (Portland, Or.) afc2009001_0068
Florida Avenue Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0181
Friendship Central Community Church (Chattanooga, Tenn.) afc2009001_0300
Galilee Baptist Church (Suitland, Md.) afc2009001_0139
Germantown Mennonite Church (Philadelphia, Pa.) afc2009001_0182
Giurgevich, Muri (Lexington, Ky.) afc2009001_0030
Golden Valley United Methodist Church (Bostic, N.C.) afc2009001_0045
Good Samaritan Center (Pinellas Park, Fla.) afc2009001_0248
Goodloe Memorial Unitarian Universalist Congregation (Bowie, Md.) afc2009001_0223
Grace Cathedral (San Francisco, Calif.) afc2009001_0194
Greater Imani Church and Christian Center (Memphis, Tenn.) afc2009001_0292
Greater New Hope Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0240
Harbor Unitarian Universalist Congregation (Muskegon, Mich.) afc2009001_0042
Harned, Roger afc2009001_0002
Harvest Church (Elk Grove, Calif.) afc2009001_0010
Heart for the World Christian Center (Aurora, Colo.) afc2009001_0097
Henry David Thoreau Unitarian Universalist Congregation (Stafford, Tex.) afc2009001_0070
Hertford United Methodist Church (Hertford, N.C.) afc2009001_0074
Highland Presbyterian Church (Louisville, Ky.) afc2009001_0276
Hindu Temple of Metropolitan Washington afc2009001_0173
Holy Faith Church (Saline, Mich.) afc2009001_0296
Horn Lake High School (Horn Lake, Miss.) afc2009001_0239
Iglesia Cristiana Hispana, Discipulos de Cristo (Anniston, Ala.) afc2009001_0089
Iman, USA afc2009001_0001
Immanuel United Church of Christ (Sedalia, Mo.) afc2009001_0263
Insight Atlanta afc2009001_0170
Interdenominational Ministerial Coalition (Louisville, Ky.) afc2009001_0301
Islamic Center of Pittsburgh afc2009001_0086
Isle of Patmos Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0289
Jewish Community Center of Harrison (Harrison, N.Y.) afc2009001_0027
Johnson Ferry Baptist Church (Marietta, Ga.) afc2009001_0174
Judson Memorial Church (New York, N.Y.) afc2009001_0075
Kittamaqundi Community Church (Columbia, Md.) afc2009001_0219
La Canada Congregational Church (La Canada Flintridge, Calif.) afc2009001_0151
Laguna Niguel Presbyterian Church (Laguna Niguel, Calif.) afc2009001_0176
Lake View Terrace American Baptist Church (Lake View Terrace, Calif.) afc2009001_0117
Lee Heights Community Church (Cleveland, Ohio) afc2009001_0078
Leftist Marching Band (Portsmouth, New Hampshire) afc2009001_0256
Les Tres Santos Reyes (Baltimore, Maryland) afc2009001_0125
Light of the World Christian Church (Indianapolis, Ind.) afc2009001_0179
Lincoln Street United Methodist Church (Portland, Or.) afc2009001_0287
Lindsay Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0206
Little River United Church of Christ (Annandale, Va.) afc2009001_0034
Little Union Baptist Church (Shreveport, La.) afc2009001_0085
Lockport United Church of Christ (Lockport, N.Y.) afc2009001_0052
Love Life Christian Fellowship Church (Ellenwood, Ga.) afc2009001_0186
Lovely Valley Baptist Church (Wirtz, Va.) afc2009001_0209
Lutheran Church of the Master (Los Angeles, Calif.) afc2009001_0087
Lutheran Church of the Newtons (Newton, Mass.) afc2009001_0094
Machar: The Washington Congregation for Secular Humanistic Judaism afc2009001_0020 afc2009001_0080
Manchester United Methodist Church (Manchester, Mo.) afc2009001_0213
Marlow United Methodist Church (Summerdale, Ala.) afc2009001_0062 afc2009001_0082
Marvin Memorial United Methodist Church (Silver Spring, Md.) afc2009001_0060
Mason United Methodist Church (Tacoma, Wash.) afc2009001_0101
Memorial Baptist Church (Hartford, Conn.) afc2009001_0260
Memorial Church Harvard University (Cambridge, Mass.) afc2009001_0104
Metropolitan Community Church of Northern Virginia (Fairfax, Va.) afc2009001_0267
Metropolitan Seventh-Day Adventist Church (Hyattsville, Md.) afc2009001_0280
Milton Seventh-Day Adventist Church (Milton-Freewater, Or.) afc2009001_0250
The Ministry of UNI United News and Information (Pasadena, California) afc2009001_0053
Morningside Presbyterian Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0018
Mount Helm Baptist Church (Jackson, Miss.) afc2009001_0144
Mount Hope Baptist Church (Prince George, Va.) afc2009001_0140
Mount Olive C.M.E. Church (Fort Valley, Ga.) afc2009001_0255
Mount Tipton Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Brighton, Tenn.) afc2009001_0103
Mount Zion United Methodist Church (Hamilton, Va.) afc2009001_0198
Mt. Ennon Baptist Church (Clinton, Md.) afc2009001_0188
Mt. Level Missionary Baptist Church (Durham, N.C.) afc2009001_0214
Mt. Sinai Baptist Church (Whistler, Ala.) afc2009001_0177
Mt. Zion Baptist Church (LaFayette, Ga.) afc2009001_0175
National Sorority of Phi Delta Kappa, Inc. Alpha Xi Chapter (Cleveland, Ohio) afc2009001_0303
Nehar Shalom Community Synagogue (Jamaica Plain, Mass.) afc2009001_0006
Neighborhood Unitarian Universalist Church (Pasadena, Calif.) afc2009001_0229-230
New Hope Baptist Church (Grand Rapids, Mich.) afc2009001_0265
New Jerusalem Church (Pretty Prairie, Kan.) afc2009001_0247
New Life Anointed Ministries International (Woodbridge, Va.) afc2009001_0185
New Mount Olive Baptist Church (Fort Lauderdale, Fla.) afc2009001_0043
New Philadelphia African Methodist Episcopal Church (Rancho Dominguez, Calif.) afc2009001_0183
Nineteenth Street Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0141
Noble Road Presbyterian Church (Cleveland Heights, Ohio) afc2009001_0041
Oakhurst Presbyterian Church (Decatur, Ga.) afc2009001_0208
Olive Branch Interfaith Peace Partnership (Nyack, N.Y.) afc2009001_0189
Original Providence Baptist Church (Chicago, Ill.) afc2009001_0055
ORS Multimidia Interativa Ltda. (Salvador, Brazil) afc2009001_0205
Our Lady Star of the Sea Catholic Church (New Orleans, La.) afc2009001_0191
Outreach for Jesus Church and Christian Education Center, Inc. afc2009001_0249
Parish Church of Christ the King (Portage, Mich.) afc2009001_0148
Positive Living Center (Oakhurst, Calif.) afc2009001_0010 afc2009001_0149
Progressive Baptist Church (New Orleans, La.) afc2009001_0147
Providence Missionary Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0098
Red Oak Grove Baptist Church (Modoc, S.C.) afc2009001_0210
The Residences at Thomas Circle (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0215
River47 Church (Orange, Calif.) afc2009001_0302
Rock Springs United Methodist Church (Lawrenceville, Ga.) afc2009001_0145
Saint Peter Missionary Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0167
Savage Memorial Presbyterian Church (Portland, Or.) afc2009001_0285
Seaside Center for Spiritual Living (Encinitas, Calif.) afc2009001_0061
Shiloh Baptist Church (Bennettsville, South Carolina) afc2009001_0156
Shiloh Baptist Church (Plainfield, N.J.) afc2009001_0268
Smith, Rev. Jean (Ft. Washington, Maryland) afc2009001_0259
Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Kansas City, Mo.) afc2009001_0264
St. Alban's Episcopal Church (Annandale, Va.) afc2009001_0127
St. Andrew's Church, Presbyterian Church of East Africa (Nairobi, Kenya) afc2009001_0291
St. Andrew's Episcopal Church (Fullerton, Calif.) afc2009001_0257
St. Augustine's Episcopal Church (Kingston, R.I.) afc2009001_0118
St. Francis' Episcopal Church (Dunellen, N.J.) afc2009001_0005
St. James AME Zion Church (Cincinnati, Ohio) afc2009001_0284
St. James Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Columbus, Ga.) afc2009001_0201
St. James United Church of Christ (Limerick, Pa.) afc2009001_0051
St. John A.M.E. Zion Church (Odenton, Md.) afc2009001_0024
St. John Progressive Missionary Baptist Church (Tampa, Fla.) afc2009001_0203
St. John's Episcopal Church (Hempstead, N.Y.) afc2009001_0040
St. Luke's Episcopal Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0168
St. Mark Presbyterian Church (Portland, Or.) afc2009001_0054
St. Mark United Methodist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0116
St. Mark's Church (Washington, D.C.: Episcopal) afc2009001_0009 afc2009001_0112
St. Mark's United Church of Christ (Baltimore, Md.) afc2009001_0121
St. Mary's Church (Rochester, N.Y.) afc2009001_0225
St. Paul Baptist Church (Oxnard, Calif.) afc2009001_0224
St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Bailey's Crossroads, Va.) afc2009001_0015
St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Oakland, Calif.) afc2009001_0073
St. Paul's On-the-Hill Episcopal Church (Saint Paul, Minn.) afc2009001_0099
St. Peter A.M.E Church (Fort Valley, Ga.) afc2009001_0277
St. Stephen United Methodist Church (Arlington, Tex.) afc2009001_0251
St. Thomas Episcopal Church (Chicago, Illinois) afc2009001_0274
Starr King Unitarian Universalist Church (Hayward, Calif.) afc2009001_0090
Stewart Memorial Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Indianapolis, Ind.) afc2009001_0095
Sun City Jewish Congregation (Palm Desert, Calif.) afc2009001_0048
Temple Beth Am (Margate, Fla.) afc2009001_0019
Temple Beth David (Rochester, N.Y.) afc2009001_0242
Temple Beth Sholom (Miami Beach, Fla.) afc2009001_0031
Temple Emanuel (Beverly Hills, Calif.) afc2009001_0200
Temple Hillel B'nai Torah (West Roxbury, Mass.) afc2009001_0216
Temple Sinai (Sumter, S.C.) afc2009001_0138
Third Street Church of God (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0190
Third Unitarian Church of Chicago afc2009001_0079
Travelers Rest Missionary Baptist Church (Morrow, Ga.) afc2009001_0304
Trinity Baptist Church of Metro Atlanta (Decatur, Ga.) afc2009001_0273
Trinity Church (Boston, Mass.) afc2009001_0036
Trinity Presbyterian Church (San Jose, Calif.) afc2009001_0056
Union Baptist Church (Easton, Md.) afc2009001_0144
Unitarian Church of Barneveld (Barneveld, N.Y.) afc2009001_0245
Unitarian Universalist Church of Asheville (Asheville, N.C.) afc2009001_0069
Unitarian Universalist Church of Delaware County (Media, Pa.) afc2009001_0057
Unitarian Universalist Church of Evansville (Evansville, Ind.) afc2009001_0258
Unitarian Universalist Church of Jacksonville (Jacksonville, Fla.) afc2009001_0067
Unitarian Universalist Church of Kent (Kent, Ohio) afc2009001_0115
Unitarian Universalist Church of Lexington (Lexington, Ky.) afc2009001_0211 afc2009001_0237
Unitarian Universalist Church of Loudon (Leesburg, Va.) afc2009001_0122
Unitarian Universalist Church of Nashua (Nashua, N.H.) afc2009001_0084
Unitarian Universalist Church of Palo Alto (Palo Alto, Calif.) afc2009001_0207
Unitarian Universalist Church of Tucson (Tucson, Arizona) afc2009001_0065
Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Danbury (Danbury, Conn.) afc2009001_0212
Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Ames (Ames, Iowa) afc2009001_0076
Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Boca Raton (Boca Raton, Fla.) afc2009001_0152
Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Door County (Sister Bay, Wis.) afc2009001_0252
Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Harford County (Churchville, Md.) afc2009001_0286
Unitarian Universalist Meeting of South Berkshire (Great Barrington, Mass.) afc2009001_0023
United Centers for Spiritual Living (Golden, Colo.) afc2009001_0163
United Christian Parish (Reston, Va.) afc2009001_0293
United Methodist Church of Santa Cruz (Santa Cruz, Calif.) afc2009001_0297
United Methodist Church of Spring Valley (Spring Valley, N.Y.) afc2009001_0166
Unity Church of Harrisburg (Enola, Pa.) afc2009001_0137
Unity Palo Alto Community Church (Palo Alto, Calif.) afc2009001_0228
Unity Presbyterian Church (Denver, N.C.) afc2009001_0092
Universalist Church (West Hartford, Conn.) afc2009001_0184
Universalist Unitarian Church of Joliet (Joliet, Ill.) afc2009001_0072
University Christian Church (San Diego, Calif.) afc2009001_0202
Valley Outreach Synagogue (Las Vegas, Nev.) afc2009001_0044
Vedanta Society of St. Louis (Mo.) afc2009001_0266
Vedanta Society of Kansas City (Mo.) afc2009001_0253
Victory for the World Church (Stone Mountain, Ga.) afc2009001_0107
Village Church of Westwood Lutheran (Los Angeles, Calif.) afc2009001_0187
Vivekananda Vedanta Society of Chicago afc2009001_0196
Wakefield Lynnfield United Methodist Church (Wakefield, Mass.) afc2009001_0298-0299
Walker, Rev. Anthony (Spencer, Oklahoma) afc2009001_0233
Wallace Memorial Baptist Church (Knoxville, Tenn.) afc2009001_0261
Ward African Methodist Episcopal Church (Los Angeles, Calif.) afc2009001_0026
Washington Area Secular Humanists, Inc. afc2009001_0035
Washington Ethical Society (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0111
Washington National Cathedral (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0295
Waters United Methodist Church (Oxford, Md.) afc2009001_0178
Wellesley Hills Congregational Church (Wellesley, Mass.) afc2009001_0126
West Hunter Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0102
Western Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0047
Westminster Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0135
Westmoreland Congregational Church (Bethesda, Md.) afc2009001_0008
Westwood Hills Christian Church (Los Angeles, Calif.) afc2009001_0063
Wheat Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0162
World Peace Prayer Society (Wasaic, N.Y.) afc2009001_0039
Wyben Union Church (Westfield, Mass.) afc2009001_0032
Yale Avenue Christian Church (Tulsa, Okla.) afc2009001_0159
Yale University. Divinity School afc2009001_0143
Zion "Goshert's" United Church of Christ (Lebanon, Pa.) afc2009001_0059
Zion Hill Baptist Church (Youngstown, Ohio) afc2009001_0236
Zion Progress Baptist Church (Detroit, Mich.) afc2009001_0281
Zlotkin, Jean M. (San Francisco, Calif.) afc2009001_0110